<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bskdanys blog</title>
    <link>https://bskdany.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bskdanys blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:23:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bskdany.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>https://bskdany.com/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 08:32:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bskdany.com/whoami/</guid>
      <description>Hey!
I&amp;rsquo;m just a guy that somehow got involved with computers and everything that has to do with them.
Right now I&amp;rsquo;m experimenting with random stuff trying to find what I like, in the past two years I did an android app, a game in unity, web scrapers, trading bots with the lean engine, websites, a chess robot, setup servers etc
At this moment I mainly code in Python but I have knowledge of C, C++, Java, Kotlin and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chess Robot</title>
      <link>https://bskdany.com/posts/chess-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bskdany.com/posts/chess-robot/</guid>
      <description>Christmas break just started, 2021 was about to end and instead of going to ski I had to stay home because my brother passed me Covid, it would be a shame if a friend of mine starts begging me to help him write the code for his robotics graduation project that was due two weeks prior.
Robot that plays chess, great project to choose if you are a complete beginner to everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abusing Bluetooth Speakers</title>
      <link>https://bskdany.com/posts/abusing-bluetooth-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:41:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bskdany.com/posts/abusing-bluetooth-speakers/</guid>
      <description>One day in April 2022 I noticed how a speaker used by a restaurant close by had the pairing mode always on, I obviously found it fun to connect to it every time I was close by and play Scotland Forever at max volume, making the waiters run around confused&amp;hellip;
Anyways, that made me wonder, how many more of those speakers can be found? I already had a plan in mind, an android app that automatically scans, pairs, connects and plays loud music on whatever it can connect to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Commit</title>
      <link>https://bskdany.com/posts/initial-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 22:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bskdany.com/posts/initial-commit/</guid>
      <description>I hope this thing is working, I have never done anything like this before but hey, what better way of showing the stuff you&amp;rsquo;re doing than a blog on the internet that no one will probably find or read.
Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a sort of therapeutical writing about what is happening in my projects so that I can organize my mind better, rubber ducky sort of thing.
I have no expectations on this so at this point why not?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
